# Ton Geatman



jonlyeatman@gmail.com



MI/TX/REMOTE



404-423-7274

github.com/Yeatman51



linkedin.com/in/jon-yeatman



http://www.jonlyeatman.com

#### SUMMARY

Graphic Designer with a passion for UI/UX design focusing on an exceptional experience for end-all users. As an experienced business owner comes a strong understanding of business operations, the importance of teamwork and detailed planning. Offering 5 years of expertise overseeing individual projects and brand development collections with unique custom artwork.

Strengths: Leadership, Out-of-the-Box Thinking, Strategic, Highly-Motivated

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Sketch, Microsoft Office, Git, GitHub, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material-UI, JavaScript, React, jQuery, APIs, JSON, AJAX, Responsive Design, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL

### PERSONAL SKILLS

Logo Design, Content Creation, Web Design, Mobile Design, Photography, Strong Leadership, Verbal Communications, Self-Management, Empathic, Analytical, Highly-Organized, Divergent-Thinker, Detailed-Oriented, Strong Work-Ethic

## EDUCATION

Full-Stack Development Certification, 2021 MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY, Lansing, MI

# PROJECTS

WallPro | Deployed Link: http://www.WallPro.net | Repository: https://github.com/mbussert/shaw-ppc

A full-stack web application created in React to assist clients in calculating square footage measurements for wall installation material deliverables on behalf of the design company. Uses Sass, MySQL, Material-UI, JavaScript, NodeMailer, React Player, Express, Node.js

Axios, Sequelize, Passport

Treat Yo'Shelf | Deployed Link: <a href="https://treatyourshelf.herokuapp.com/">https://github.com/hstor3/treat-yo-shelf</a>
A user-friendly app that lets you organize your books and treat your bookshelf utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Handlebars

DinGen | Deployed Application: <a href="https://yeatman51.github.io/DinGen-Web/">https://yeatman51.github.io/dingen-web/</a> A web application built in an agile team environment aiming to simplify a user's decision-making process for dinner selection. This application leverages two third-party APIs, HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, jQuery UI Library & Font Awesome

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Owner/Operator

Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC 2018 - Present

# Graphic Design Artist

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC 2017 - 2019

## Infantryman

Michigan Army National Guard 2013 - 2017

- Had a company standard of 100% production quality/error handling
- Maximized immediate turn-around by minimizing unnecessary overhead
- Partnered with local third-party vendors to create a streamline process for clients
- Quality relationship building with clients for trustworthy product delivery
- Consistently delivered close to 500 designs quarterly per clientele
- Optimized processes working with a variety of garments, inks and merchandise
- Streamlined production pipeline for multi faceted items
- · Displayed a high level of competence and professionalism under stressful situations
- Supervised, trained and ensured the safety and welfare of a 4-person team, maintaining a 100% safety record